{"question":"MC","answer":"A","score":10,"type":"SINGLE","optionA":"1","optionB":"2","optionC":"3","optionD":"4","id":1732190875889}
{"question":"MC2","answer":"A","score":10,"type":"SINGLE","optionA":"1","optionB":"2","optionC":"3","optionD":"4","id":1732190878849}
{"question":"MC3","answer":"A","score":10,"type":"SINGLE","optionA":"1","optionB":"2","optionC":"3","optionD":"4","id":1732190882208}
{"question":"MMC","answer":"AC","score":10,"type":"MULTIPLE","optionA":"1","optionB":"2","optionC":"3","optionD":"4","id":1732190899896}
{"question":"MMC2","answer":"AC","score":10,"type":"MULTIPLE","optionA":"1","optionB":"2","optionC":"3","optionD":"4","id":1732190917922}
{"question":"MMC3","answer":"AC","score":10,"type":"MULTIPLE","optionA":"1","optionB":"2","optionC":"3","optionD":"4","id":1732190923683}
{"question":"TF","answer":"T","score":10,"type":"TRUE_FALSE","optionA":"True","optionB":"False","optionC":"","optionD":"","id":1732190935182}
{"question":"TF2","answer":"T","score":10,"type":"TRUE_FALSE","optionA":"True","optionB":"False","optionC":"","optionD":"","id":1732190940004}
{"question":"TF3","answer":"T","score":10,"type":"TRUE_FALSE","optionA":"True","optionB":"False","optionC":"","optionD":"","id":1732190944682}
{"question":"SQ1","answer":"QAZ","score":10,"type":"SHORT_Q","optionA":"","optionB":"","optionC":"","optionD":"","id":1732190955162}
{"question":"SQ2","answer":"WSX","score":10,"type":"SHORT_Q","optionA":"","optionB":"","optionC":"","optionD":"","id":1732190963180}
{"question":"SQ3","answer":"EDC","score":10,"type":"SHORT_Q","optionA":"","optionB":"","optionC":"","optionD":"","id":1732190968879}
